89… 144.
233.
- Yoo-shin, Dad's boss is calling.
- Faye-bo's dad.
Faye-bo's dad…
Got it.
What number comes before 233?
144, 233.
377.
610.
987.
1,597.
2,574.
That's wrong.
2,584.
It's so cold here.
The air is terrible too.
I don't know why, but everything changed
when I walked out.
Everything changed.
But the roads here
look just like ours.
I'M FINE. DON'T WORRY.
REST UP, SCHOOL TOMORROW.
MOM
Your call has been forwarded to…
Your call has been forwarded to voicemail…
Hello? Xiaoqi.
Do you know what time it is?
Better be important.
Please see if my mom's home.
She was there when I got my headphones.
It's hard to explain.
Just check if she's there.
THE AIR QUALITY IS AT A HAZARDOUS LEVEL.
PLEASE AVOID GOING OUTSIDE.
Yu-jhen.
I'll go now.
Why do you look so scared?
You're not even wearing a mask.
Aren't you afraid to die?
Do you know her?
Who is she?
And him?
Wow, where was this taken?
Edited, right?
The air looks so fresh.
I wanna take a deep breath.
Is An-an all right?
Early shift tomorrow?
Then go get some sleep.
If you fall asleep at work,
you'll get fired.
Is An-an off early tomorrow?
I can pick him up at noon
and bring him to the library,
so he can skip after-school care.
YIPING LIBRARY
Mei-ling,
your reactions are so slow today,
even more than usual.
What's wrong?
No, it's okay.
Thanks. I've already made arrangements.
YOUR MOM'S IN THE CAR!
CALLING
MOM
Your call has been forwarded to voicemail.
Leave a message after the beep or hang up.
Did you check online first?
No, I didn't.
Next time you borrow a book,
reserve it online first. It's faster.
Let me find it for you.
It should be…
here.
Yes, thank you.
No problem.
Mei-ling?
Cancel the peptides I ordered.
- He says it's too expensive.
- No. I've placed the order.
Just sell it…
WELCOME TO YIPING ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
THE CURRENT AIR QUALITY
IS UNHEALTHY FOR ALL GROUPS.
PLEASE LIMIT OUTDOOR ACTIVITIES
An-an's mom?
Come on. Let's go.
An-an's mom. I thought An-an
was going to after-school care.
Good thing you came.
He brought a baseball to school
and someone got hit.
The school doesn't allow it,
especially outside in this haze.
So please remind An-an
about this next time, okay?
- An-an.
- What's wrong?
- What happened?
It's okay. Lie down.
Breathe slowly, An-an. An-an.
Breathe slowly. An-an's mom, help me.
Don't rush.
Don't rush. Take slow breaths.
Take slow breaths.
That's it.
Keep breathing, An-an.
That's it. Take slow breaths.
An-an, do you know where you are?
Take your time.
Mom.
Skipping class again?
- Didn't I tell you I'd come?
- Lower your voice.
You forgot already?
Rest somewhere. I've got work to do.
You even forgot I bought you coffee?
YIPING ELEMENTARY,
HSU LI-AN
Mom?
Where's your scooter?
You didn't ride here?
I wanted to walk with you today.
Aren't we going home? Where are we going?
Yes, we will go home. We will.
Mom, you're squeezing too hard.
My hand hurts.
Sorry.
Mom, what's wrong today?
Did Dad upset you?
Or did I do something wrong again?
No.
It's nothing.
You did nothing wrong.
Then why are you sad?
Mom's okay.
You're such a good kid.
Let's go.
253, 254, 255, 256,
257, 258, 259,
260, 261, 262, 263, 264, 265…
Mom, I don't want to see a doctor.
I'm really okay. I don't want to go.
Okay, we won't see a doctor then.
Excuse me.
Hi, Auntie.
Dr. Sun is on break.
Go to a hospital if you need a doctor.
An-an!
It really is you.
I thought I was mistaken.
Hi, Uncle. Mom picked me up today.
You didn't ride today?
Mom didn't ride today.
Are we walking home?
Walking? It's too far. I'll take you home.
Yay!
We can go home ourselves.
Don't worry about it.
It's no trouble. None at all.
Wait for me a moment.
Mom.
Mom!
PSYCHIATRY CLINIC
- Due on March 11th.
- Thanks.
When did you buy me coffee?
You really forgot?
I even lent you 200 bucks.
You have a twin sister?
Hi, teacher.
This is An-an's mom. Is An-an okay?
Let me take you out to eat.
My appointments start at 3:00,
so I have time.
Mei-ling?
Mom?
Uncle wants to know
if we're eating together.
No, thank you.
I'll take Yoo…
I'll take An-an home.
- We're going on vacation.
- Really?
Is Dad going with us?
When we get home,
we'll talk it over with Dad.
If he agrees,
we'll leave here.
"Leave"? Where are you going?
An-an isn't in any condition
to travel right now.
I can.
An-an, can you handle it?
What if you have another seizure?
We'd be so worried
if Mom and Dad couldn't find a doctor.
We'll look after him.
Thanks for caring.
I checked. She's not in the backyard.
I'll check the basement.
I'll call you later.
Mom!
Are you in there?
Mom?
- Bye, Uncle.
- Okay, head inside.
What's wrong today?
You're acting strange.
When can we meet again?
I need to talk to you.
Level five?
Mom, the smog is coming! Get inside!
Okay.
Go inside. We'll meet another time.
But I forgot to bring the keys.
I've got it.
Mom, I told Grandma we're going out today.
Is Dad coming home? When?
"Grandma"?
Mom, look outside.
What happened?
Yoo-shin. come on. Let's go.
Hurry up. Hurry.
An-an, let's go.
- Come on, let's go. Hurry up.
- No!
- Come on.
- I don't want to!
- Come.
An-an, sweetheart.
- I don't want to!
- Come on.
Hurry up!
I don't want to!
No…
The door is unlocked.
She's back.
Mom, where were you?
You didn't answer. We were so worried.
An-an!
- An-an!
- Mom.
Who was supposed to pick you up?
She left.
You knew she wasn't me.
- You still let her take you!
- I didn't know!
I thought she was you.
She looked just like you
and was wearing your jacket.
I was so close.
So close to bringing Yoo-shin back.
So close.
Is she the mom in the mirror?
I told you, she's not your mom.
I was afraid of losing you,
that's why I hit you.
Thief!
I'm talking to you.
Don't take my son!
Li Yun.
Are you all right?
I was in meetings all day.
Yu-jhen was worried sick
and rushed back after two classes.
Why ignore me?
- I'll go see her.
- No need. She's back in Taipei.
She has class tomorrow.
Why didn't you tell me?
Dr. Jian called.
She couldn't find you. She was worried.
I lost my phone.
I left it there…
at the library.
I know.
Yu-jhen said
you went to another world.
Yes.
You don't believe me.
Dr. Jian wants to see you tomorrow.
I'll go with you.
Or we can find another doctor
- in Taipei.
- Look at this jacket.
You've never seen me wear it, right?
I brought it from another world.
And this name tag belongs to An-an.
See? His name is Xu Li-an.
Everyone calls him An-an.
You were sleepwalking.
- Where did you find it?
- Ｎo, I wasn't sleepwalking. This is real.
I held Yoo-shin's hand.
It was warm and soft.
It felt real.
It's true. I went to another world.
I opened the door and ended up there.
I don't know why…
What time is it?
Nearly 3:00.
The mirror cracked at 2:00 a.m.
- I came back in the afternoon--
- I haven't slept.
The mirror didn't crack.
I'll go with you tomorrow.
Why not sleep in?
I got enough sleep.
What happened?
Something fell into the drain.
What did you drop?
My ring.
- I'll take care of the drain later--
- Can you fix it?
Don't bother.
It's filthy in there.
I'll call someone later.
Aren't you working today?
I'll stay with you.
I took a week off.
I'll go with you to Dr. Jian.
Did you fall asleep before you went there?
I wasn't dreaming.
I believe you.
Can you tell me what happened?
What was that other world like?
Did you see anything you'll never forget?
I saw you.
You saw me?
You're a nurse
at a clinic.
But you… seemed so distant.
The doctor looked
just like Jian-cheng's friend.
He's a real estate agent here.
It's true.
That doctor and Mei-ling seemed close,
like they had something going on.
If it wasn't a dream,
then a hallucination?
Let's let her finish, okay?
Dr. Jian,
thanks for your patience. I'm really okay.
I'm really fine.
I haven't felt
this clear-headed in three years.
Sorry to take up your time. Thank you.
One of her pills is Stilnox.
It causes sleepwalking.
Could that be what happened last night?
She's taken it before and slept well.
Sleepwalkers don't know
what they're doing.
She remembers everything clearly,
so not sleepwalking.
You doubt my professional opinion?
That's not what I meant.
I'm just worried.
How can I help her?
I think you're the key
to her recovery.
I'll prescribe medication,
but it takes at least seven days to work.
Can you talk to her?
I'll arrange counseling.
Will you come with her?
I'll take you to get a new phone later.
There's an old one at home I can use.
Then let's go home.
- I need to pack my things.
- I'll go with you.
Next time, I'll definitely bring Yoo-shin…
I'll bring An-an back
and prove it to you.
If you're telling the truth,
An-an is someone else's child.
Is it right to take him away?
That's heaven's gift for my loss.
Li Yun!
THE APPOINTMENT IS AT 2 PM
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW.
JUST BE PATIENT AND LET HER SPEAK.
OKAY.
Sorry, bro.
Waiting long?
That last customer
asked so many questions.
I called you last minute.
When can we sign?
I've been home lately.
Let's find a time to go over it.
Have you thought it through, bro?
Why do you ask?
I said your price was fine.
I know.
But didn't you say yesterday
you weren't selling?
No, I didn't.
Bro, don't joke.
We were here yesterday.
You held my hand
and said you weren't selling.
Don't you remember?
I really didn't.
Are you free tonight?
Yes.
Let's meet tonight.
Want a drink?
I'm good. I'll just have water.
The door is unlocked.